

Harold Rita

Layout Artist & Web Administrator (1 year 4 months) **BOHOL ISLAND STATE UNIVERSITY RESEARCH JOURNAL**

Journal of Agricultural Development and Biodiveristy Conservation

09168558252 | letswrite14@gmail.com | Barangay Zamora Bilar Bohol

Website: coloftech.com and promisesorrynotes.xyz

Experiences

Aug 2016 - Present

Layout & Web Administrator - Research and Development Online Journal

(1 year 4 months)

Bohol Island State University - Bilar Campus | Bohol, Philippines

Job description Website administrator and layout of articles, Trainer

> for online journal editorial workflow www.bisuonlinejournals.com

Nov 2015 - Aug 2016

Office staff - encoder

Website

Job description

(10 months)

China Geo-engineering Corporation Phil. | Occidental Mindoro Highway Project

Industry Architectural Services / Interior Designing

Encoder of daily accomplishment and book binding

of monthly report, with AUTOCAD

Apr 2014 - Nov 2015

Marketing Assistant/OIC

(1 year 8 months) Motortrade Nationwide Corporation | Occidental Mindoro, Philippines

> Motorcycle dealer Job description Sales Marketing

Jun 2013 - Feb 2014

Web Programmer

(9 months) ISURE Company | Quezon City, Philippines

> Industry Multi-level Marketing

Job description Website Developer (project based)

May 2012 - May 2013 Sales Marketing

G. Pineda Enterprises | Quezon City, Philippines

Industry Rice Dealer and Multi-level Marketing Job description Sales Marketing and website administrator

Jun 2011 - Mar 2012

(1 year 1 month)

Computer Operator

(10 months) Extreme Print Arts and Computer Services | Occidental Mindoro, Philippines

> Industry Computer / Information Technology (Hardware)

Specialization IT/Computer - Hardware

Nov 2008 - Mar 2010

Student Assistant

(1 year 5 months) Occidental Mindoro State College | Occidental Mindoro, Philippines

> Industry Education Specialization General Work

Oct 2008 - Mar 2010

Visual Artist

(1 year 6 months) Eyetech Publication | Occidental Mindoro, Philippines

Industry College Printing / Publishing Specialization Drawing and writing poetry

Skills

Intermediate Web development | PHP Programming (codeigiter), MySQL Database, JavaScript, CSS, HTML

Intermediate Layout | Photoshop, Indesign, MS Publisher

Intermediate Animation | Micromedia Flash 8

Intermediate Video and Audio editing | Cyberlink Powerdirector

Other information

Seminar/ Workshop/ Conferences

Resource Speaker | Seminar - Workshop on Online Journal System in Editorial Workflow |

Bohol Island State University - Main Campus

Resource Speaker | Seminar - Workshop on Online Journal System in Editorial Workflow | Bohol Island State University - Bilar Campus

Facilitator | Image processing Rater Analysis and Geo Spatial Analysis | Bohol Island State Univers Facilitator | Seminar-workshop on Advances and mesurement principles in plant water -relations | Bohol Island State University

Trainee | Learn to Ride Safely | Motortrade Nationwide Corporation

Trainee | Achieve Personal Excellence | Motortrade Nationwide Corporation

Trainee|Productive Work Attitude | Motortrade Nationwide Corporation

Achievements and Contributions

Coach for table tennis event (SCUAA) | Bohol Island State University Bilar Campus | Zamora

Bilar Bohol

Officer-in-charge (6months) | Motortrade Nationwide Corporatrion - Sablayan Branch |

Sablyan Occidental Mindoro

Assistant coach for athetics event (INTRAMURAL) | Occidental Mindoro State College | San Jose Occidental Mindoro

Varsity | Silver and Bronze Medalis in Track n field event at Regional olympic (PASUC IV A &

B) | Occidental Mindoro State College | San Jose Occidental Mindoro
Athlete of the year 2007| Regional Player | Track n field event | Ligaya National High School |

Ligaya Sablayan Occidental Mindoro

Hobbies and Interest Playing table tennis and basketball

Drawing and Sketching

Playing Guitar

Composing song and poetry
Reading and writing short story

Education

²⁰¹² Occidental Mindoro State College

Bachelor's/College Degree in Computer Science/Information Technology | San Jose Occidental Mindoro Philippines

²⁰¹⁰ TESDA 8 Regional Training Center(ISUZU Training Center)

National Certificate 1 in Automotive Servicing | Tacloban City Philippines

²⁰⁰⁷ Ligaya National High School

Secondary Education | Ligaya Sablayan Occidental Mindoro Philippines

²⁰⁰³ Ligaya Elementary School

Primary Education | Ligaya Sablayan Occidental Mindoro Philippines

Languages

Proficiency level: 0 - Poor, 10 - Excellent
Language Spoken Written
Filipino (Primary) 10 10
English 7 7
Visayan 3 3

About Me

 Age
 28 years

 Birthday
 July 17 1989

Birthplace Ligaya Sablayan Occidental Philippines

Nationality Philippines
Height 5'4"
Weight 53 kg
Civil status Single
Nationality Philippines
Mother name Thelma Rita
Father name Roberto Rita

Character Reference Shiela Tabuno Address Bohol Island State University - Bilar Campus

Contact No. 09335786385

Name Wilborn Joy Arestilla

Address Bohol Island State University - Bilar Campus

Contact No. 09486422642

Name **Agustin Ancog**

Address Bohol Island State University - Bilar Campus

Contact No. 09081721566

 $I\ hereby\ certify\ that\ the\ above\ information\ are\ true\ and\ correct\ to\ the\ best\ of\ my\ knowledge\ and\ belief\ and\ that\ not$ withheld any pertinent facts and information.

> Harold V. Rita Applicant